>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 你在想为什么，谢谢你问我，我有三个
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And you're wondering
why and thanks for asking, I have three
你为什么总是更喜欢这件事情
reasons why you should always prefer this
thing that's gonna take you more time and
努力把这些名字写出来吧
effort to write out all those
names to those functions, right?
我们知道计算机科学的经典难题之一就是
We know that one of the classic hard
problems in computer science is naming
你跟我说我要把这些名字都给我
things, and, you're telling me I gotta
go come up with all these names.
相信我，我在同一条船上，每次写功能，我都不知道
Trust me, I'm in the same boat, every time
I write a function, I'm like, I don't know
怎么称呼呢，不能叫个好名字，我明白。
what to call this thing, can't come up
with a good name, I understand that.
但是有三个原因，我想，一起做个实案，
But there are three reasons which I think,
together, make a solid case,
这一努力是至关重要的，这是必要的，
that that effort is critical,
that it's necessary,
您应该始终使用名称函数表达式。
that you should always,
always use name-function expressions.
所以数字更喜欢命名函数表达式，因为名称产生或
So number one prefer a name function
expression, because the name produces or
从自身内部创建对功能的可靠的自我引用。
creates a reliable self-reference to
the function from inside of itself.
如果要使函数递归，那么这很有用。
That is useful if you're going
to make the function recursive.
如果该函数是某种类型的事件处理程序，那么它很有用。
It's useful if that function is
an event handler of some sort and
它需要自我约束才能解除束缚
it needs to reference
itself to unbind itself.
如果您需要访问任何属性，那么它很有用
It's useful if you need to
access any properties on that
函数对象，例如其链接或其名称或该排序的其他内容。
function object such as its link or
its name or other thing of that sort.
任何时候你都可能需要自己的功能
Anytime you might need a self
reference to the function,
这个问题的唯一正确答案是它需要有一个名字
the single only right answer to that
question is, it needs to have a name.
有一些 EES6 之前的 hacks 或 Es5 pre Es5 之前的 hacks，
There were some pre ES6 sorts of hacks or
an even pre ES5 sorts of hacks,
您可以使用自变量开始调用作为函数的引用，
where you could use arguments start
calling as a reference to the function,
它没有被损坏但实际上是不推荐的
it's not broken but
essentially deprecated.
从自身内部获取功能的方法和
The way to get a reference to
a function from inside of itself and
有可靠的引用是使用函数表达式的名称。
have a reliable reference is to use
the name of your function expression.
在前面的示例中，当我具有全局变量名称时
In that previous example, when I had
a variable name that was in the global
范围，然后我就有了我的功能表达。
scope, and
then I had my function expression.
这会不会更可靠
Would it be more or less reliable for
我要在自己的范围内引用一个大理石
me to make a reference to a marble in
my own scope that is read only, or
在不只读的外层范围内引用大理石吗 ?
to reference a marble in an enclosing
scope that is not read only?
>> Kyle Simpson: 如果我想从功能的内部引用自己，并且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If I wanted to reference
myself from inside of the function, and
我自己也有自己的选择
I had the choice between referencing
myself with a marble in my own
范围，它是只读的，是我的函数表达式的名称。
scope that is read only,
the name of my function expression.
或者我可以用自己的功能来自我反省
Or I could self-reference myself with
the variable that my function had
在外部作用域中分配，这不是缺省情况下的只读。
be assigned to in the outer scope,
which isn't by default read only.
这两者中的哪一个会是更好的自我参考呢 ?
Which one of those two would
be the better self reference?
>> 扬声器 2: 第一个。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The first one.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 第一，对，你自己和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: First one,
right, the one that you own and
这是一个更可靠的自我参考。
that is read only is a more
reliable self reference.
第一，如果有任何可能的机会，你会
So, number one, if there's any possible
chance remotely that you're gonna
需要一个自我的参考，最好是把它命名。
need a self reference,
it's best to go ahead and name it.
即使你现在不需要它将来也可能需要它，
Even if you don't need it now,
you might need it in the future,
最好把它命名为第一个名字
it's best to go ahead and
name it, that's reason number one.
原因二，您应该始终选择指定的函数表达式。
Reason number two, why you should always
prefer named function expressions.
您有多少人曾经遇到过 JavaScript 异常，您必须在其中进行调试
How many of you have ever had a JavaScript
exception where you had to debug it by
查看堆栈跟踪吗 ?
looking at a stack trace?
你有多少人喜欢看到匿名的功能
Okay, how many of you love seeing
anonymous function, over and over again,
在您的堆栈跟踪中的行后面的行吗 ?
line after line in your stack traces?
尤其是当我们讨论的生产代码是迷你化的时候
Especially, when we're talking about
production code that's been minified, so
他们都说第一行 32，712 ，
they all say line 1, character 32,712,
我们都知道那是什么功能对吧
cuz we all know exactly which
function that is, right?
如果您使用函数表达式的名称，那么会发生什么情况 ?
Guess what happens if you use a name for
your function expressions?
它显示在堆栈跟踪中。
It shows up in the stack trace.
如果您使用的名称不像食物条，但就像处理用户点击一样，
If you use a good name not like food bar,
but like handle user click,
它就会出现在堆栈跟踪中
it's going to show up in the stack trace.
通过命名函数，使代码更可调试，
So automatically by naming your functions,
you make your code more debuggable,
使堆栈跟踪更可调试。
you make your stack
traces more debuggable.
说实话我曾多次研究过一个很有好处的
Truth, I have on multiple occasions,
looked at a stack trace that had good,
其中有用的语义名称，以及
useful semantic names in it, and
只要看看这些名字和名字就能告诉他的消息来源
been able to tell the source of the bug
simply by looking at the names and
什么叫什么叫什么叫什么叫什么叫什么叫什么。
the order of the functions, what didn't
get called and what did get called.
甚至都没看密码
Didn't even have to look at the code,
我立刻就知道这个病毒的名字是什么
I knew immediately what the bug
was just from having the names.
就算你得看密码你还在接近代码
And even if you do have to look at the
code, you're still approaching the code
从那个堆栈跟踪中得到的更多的精神背景比你之前的更多
with more mental context from that
stack trace than you would before.
现在我觉得这条规则
Now I think that rule in and
本身就足以证明你的职责
of itself is enough to justify
always name your functions.
我不知道你的情况，但我需要帮助我调试我的程序。
I don't know about you, but I need all
the help I can debugging my programs.
那么额外的努力就是每次我要调试的时候都要分红
So, the extra effort is gonna pay off
in dividends every time I have to debug
代码。
the code.
第二，我们希望有可调试的堆栈跟踪。
Number two,
we want to have debuggable stack traces.
第三个我个人认为这可能是最重要的
And number three, and I think personally
this might be the most important of all,
但肯定是最不明显的
but it's certainly the one
that seems least obvious or
也许对其他人更有争议
maybe it's a little more
controversial to other people.
第三个名字在你的功能上
Number three,
by putting a name on your function,
你会让那个代码更自我记录
you make that code more self-documenting.
如果我有匿名的功能我看着那个功能
If I have a function that is anonymous,
and I look at that function to figure out
这个匿名函数在做什么我得读函数体
what that anonymous function is doing,
I have to read the function body and
我还得看它被解析的地方
I also probably have to read
where it's being parsed.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我要从这两条信息中推断，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And I have to infer
from those two pieces of information,
功能的用途。
the purpose of the function.
我可以推断其处理用户单击的目的。
I may be able to infer the purposes
that it handles user clicks.
但我宁愿读者不要推断它的目的是为了处理
But I would rather the reader not have
to infer that its purpose is to handle
当我能把名字放进去的时候
user clicks when I could put a name
there that makes it completely and
毫不含糊
totally unambiguous.
名为 " 句柄用户单击 " 的功能不需要任何其他
The function named handle user
clicks doesn't require any other
读其他的代码让我明白
reading of the rest of the code,
for me to figure out,
你想让我用这个功能来处理用户的点击，是吗 ?
you want me to handle user
clicks with this function, yes?
>> 扬声器 3: 因此，这更多的最佳实践问题似乎很有说服力。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So this is more of a best
practices question seems very compelling.
然后我的第一直觉是说，好吧，我就叫这个表情
My first instinct is then to say,
okay, I'll just name the expression
我就会把这个范围的变量命名为
the same thing that I will name the
variable of the scope above, I'm assuming,
a，是否有阴影的情况 ?
a, is that a case of shadowing?
还有 b，- >> Kyle Simpson:
And b,-
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It is a case of
阴暗
shadowing.
> 演讲者 3: 在 B，可能对碎片造成极大的问题，或者
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: And at B, that's probably
incredibly problematic for debris or is
会被考虑的事情 -- >凯尔 - 辛普森: 我不考虑
that something that would be considered-
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I wouldn't consider
阴影是问题还是不是问题。
shadowing to be a problem or
not a problem.
在特定情况下，我认为您不太可能需要
In that particular scenario, I think it is
unlikely that you're gonna need to have
都是对函数的引用。
both references to the function.
也许你需要这样做你得给他们命名
Maybe you're gonna need to and if you do,
you're gonna have to name them something
不一样你现在就得躲躲避让
different, you're now gonna
have to avoid shadowing.
但在大多数情况下，如果这件事有一个明确的名称，
But in most cases, if there is one
definitive name for what this thing is,
如果你想的话现在都叫他们俩
name both of them now if you want to.
我的个人意见是对变量的函数表达式是不起作用的，
My personal opinion is don't do function
expression on the variable anyway,
做一个功能声明还有一个名字如果你要去的话
do a function declaration and there's
just one name but, if you are going
如果只有一个名字的话，那就更有道理了。
to make a variable then it probably makes
more sense if there's only one name.
但这一点也有一些警告，因为有的时候，这种功能的使用，
There are caveats to this, though, because
sometimes, the usage of that function,
它被转移到的地方或者它要做什么
where it's being passed to,
or what it's going to do,
它的目的可能与你想描述它本身的方式不同
it may have a different purpose than how
you wanna describe it, in and of itself.
所以也许会有另一个更合适的名字
So it might in fact be that there's
a different, more appropriate name for
它的功能，而不是它所分配给的属性，或者
the function, as opposed to what
property it's being assigned to, or
所分配给的变量。
what variable it's being assigned to.
因此，他们不一定相同，但有时可能有帮助吗 ?
So they are not necessarily the same,
but sometimes they might be, helpful?
好了这三个我想起来了
Good, so these three I think,
taken together,
你的功能就会被你的
make an ironclad case
that your functions would
如果您的功能被命名，那么会生成更好的代码。
make better code if your
functions are named.
现在我知道对大多数有这种情况的人有问题
Now I understand that that is problematic
for most people that have that
指以匿名方式书写功能的手指肌肉记忆。
finger muscle memory of writing
the functions anonymously.
自 JQuery 天数以来，我使用匿名功能查看了每个博客。
That I've seen every single blog since the
jQuery days, using anonymous functions.
你对匿名功能有任何访问权
That every piece of code you've ever
had any access to anonymous functions
到处都是
everywhere.
突然有一个人跟你说不不不
And all of a sudden, here's this
one guy telling you, no, no, no,
都需要名字
those all need names.
我明白，这很麻烦，麻烦，额外的工作。
I get it, that's problematic,
it's troublesome, it's extra work.
但你必须回到我所说的代码的目的
But you have to go back to what I
said about the purpose of code.
代码的用途不方便您输入。
The purpose of code is not to
be convenient for you to type.
代码的目的是让您更清楚地传达您的意图。
The purpose of code is for you to
communicate more clearly your intent.
有办法解决这些问题，但是
There are ways to solve
each of these problems but
解决这些问题的最佳方法是命名函数。
the best way to solve these
problems is to name the function.
刚才有人问我如果分配匿名功能会发生什么
So someone asked just a moment ago, what
happens if I assign an anonymous function
财产，或者变量什么的，名字发生了什么 ?
to property, or to a variable or
something, what happens to the name?
这仍然是一个匿名的功能
Well, it's still an anonymous function,
它本身也没有词法自调。
it still doesn't have a lexical
self-reference to itself.
您可以引用外部作用域中的变量吗 ?
Could you reference the variable
in the outer scope?
当然你可以但少得多可靠一点也不可信
Of course you can, but it's a little less
reliable, a little less trustable, and
我想说一点语意
I would argue a little less semantic.
它会在堆栈跟踪中显示名称吗 ?
Is it gonna show up with
a name in the stack trace?
根据该函数表达式的位置，
Depending upon where that
function expression exists,
也许能推断出一个名字
it might be able to have a name inferred.
例如，如果分配给变量，
For example,
if it's assigned to a variable,
那么一般只要没有什么复杂的破坏代码到位，
then generally as long as there isn't
some complex destructuring code in place,
一般都是用这个名字和推断来
generally it's going to just take the name
and infer that's what you mean for
堆栈跟踪的目的，但在此处是大问题， 99.9%
the purposes of the stack trace,
except here is the big problem, 99.9%
使用匿名函数表达式的所有个案都是回调。
of all cases where people use anonymous
functions expressions is as callbacks.
它们直接传递给其他函数如 .map ，然后
They pass them in line directly to
other functions like .map, .then,
所有这些猜测是什么
all those and guess what?
当您在调用位置传递函数表达式时，
When you pass a function
expression in a call position,
没有办法从上面推断任何名字
there's no way to infer any name from it.
所以你没有得到这个名字推论的好处
So you don't get the benefit
of that name inference,
您必须将其分配给变量以获取名称推论或属性。
you have to assign it to a variable to
get the name inference or to a property.
如果你想把它分配给一个变量
And if you're gonna go to the trouble
to assign it to a variable why
不只是声明吗
not just make it a declaration?
为什么写变量，然后又要写两次 ?
Why write a variable and
then have to write the name twice?
我看不出有什么理由你更喜欢做更多的工作
I don't see any reason why you should
strongly prefer making more work for
你自己也会让人更困惑
yourself and making it a little
bit more confusing for people.
而这甚至不是唯一的区别，当我们谈论提升的时候，
And that's not even the only difference,
when we talk about hoisting later we're
会发现有很大的差异
gonna see there's a big
difference in hoisting.
所以我觉得你应该喜欢用名字命名的函数声明
So I think you should prefer function
declarations with names if you're
能在一个函数表达式中传递一个名字
gonna pass in a function expression, put a
name on it just like you would have if it
是函数声明，为其指定相同的名称。
were a function declaration,
give it the same name.
现在我知道命名很难，但真正的原因是你为什么
Now I understand that naming is hard but
really the only legitimate reason why you
别给你的功能命名你太懒了或者没有创意来找个名字
don't name your functions cuz you're too
lazy or uncreative to come up with a name.
匿名函数的 preferable 没有任何原因。
There is no reason why an anonymous
function is preferrable.
没有任何自变量可以表明该名称正在提取或
There is no argument that can be made
that that name is distracting or
对代码可读性的目的无帮助。
is unhelpful for
the purposes of code readability.
任何人士在这方面所提出的论据，都是完整的。
Any argument that people have made
to that extent is complete bunk.
大家都在书和博客里都告诉你，不，不，
People tell you all over the place
in books and blogs, no, no,
不所有额外的东西都是不必要的
no, all that extra stuff
is totally unnecessary.
他们的想法是完全错误的
And they're thinking
completely wrongly about this,
他们不是在考虑好的语义名称的目的
cuz they're not thinking about
the purpose of good semantic names.
函数名的目的是告诉您此东西存在的原因。
The purpose of a function name is to
tell you why does this thing exist.
我的断言是你的程序中存在的每一项功能
My assertion is that every function
that exists in your program,
每个功能都有目的
every single function has a purpose.
如果每个函数都有一个目的，就意味着每个函数都有一个名称。
And if every function has a purpose,
it means every function has a name.
你要用那个名字来把它放进你的代码里
And it's up to you to come up with that
name and put it in your code, not make
您的代码的读者每次阅读代码时都必须将其计算出来。
the reader of your code have to figure it
out every single time they read the code.
如果你不能用这个函数来命名，
If you can not come up with a name for
the function,
这可能意味着你还不明白这个功能
it probably means that you don't
understand that function yet.
这可能意味着这个功能太复杂了
It probably means,
that function is too complex,
需要被分解成更小的碎片
and needs to be broken down into
smaller pieces until such a time
因为这些名字是完全自明的，然后把它们放在那里。
as those names are completely self
obvious, and then put them there.
当你不能去的时候它是一个更有问题的代码的领先指标
It's a leading indicator of more
problematic code when you can't
提出一个名字
come up with a name or
你能给我的名字有 14 个字就像在 Java 里一样好吗
the name that you can come up with is
14 words long like we do in Java, okay?
这通常意味着此功能在执行过多操作。
That usually means this
function is doing too much.
这里有个问题是吗
There was a question over here, yes?
>> 扬声器 4: 你是说使用匿名功能
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: So are you saying
that the use of anonymous functions
其实就是少了一点，其实都是这样。
is really just to type less,
that's really all.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这正是我要说的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's
exactly what I'm saying, and
我们下下一张幻灯片会变得更糟
it gets worse when we go
to the next slide, yes.
>> 扬声器 5: 所以听起来你肯定喜欢声明，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 5: So it sounds like you
definitely prefer declarations,
有吗，功能表达式有什么好的用法吗 ?
is there ever, is there a good use for
a function expression?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，绝对的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, absolutely,
函数表达式有时是绝对必要的。
function expression sometimes
are absolutely necessary.
我的经验法则除了你要去的地方
My personal rule of thumb,
other than places where you have to,
我的个人经验法则是我更喜欢功能宣言
my personal rule of thumb is that I prefer
function declaration if it's more than
三行代码。
three lines of code.
如果是一，两，三行代码，
If it's one, two, or three lines of code,
通常我要做一个内联函数表达式。
generally I'm gonna make that
an inline function expression.
除非这个东西需要多次调用，在这种情况下，
Unless, that thing needs to be called
multiple times, in which case,
我要把它作为一个功能宣言即使它是一条直线
I'm gonna make it a function declaration,
even if it's one line.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 但这些只是一般的指引
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: But those are just
sort of general guidelines in case,
你的飞行哩数可能随他们的不同而不同
your mileage may vary, as they say, okay?
所以你猜我还是很挣扎
So guess what, I still struggle with this,
even though for
我一直在宣扬这个信息告诉人们
years I've been preaching this message and
telling people.
你是一万零的学生听我说这事对吧
And you're the 10,000th student
to ever hear me say this, right?
我已经说了这么多年了
I've said this all over the world for
years and
我仍然挣扎在这个问题上，这就是我所使用的诡计。
I still struggle with this problem and
here's the trick that I use.
第一，我从来没有写过代码，然后我就完成了，
Number one, I don't ever write code
just once and then I'm done with it,
代码始终是一个迭代过程，我在其中对其进行重构。
code is always an iterative
process where I'm refactoring it.
当我开始写函数的时候，我几乎肯定还不知道如何和
When I start to write a function, I almost
certainly don't know yet exactly how and
那个功能会是什么或者什么结构
what that function's gonna be for
or what the structure's gonna be.
所以我承认我所提出的任何名字都不是写在
So I just accept the fact that whatever
name I come up with is not written in
石头和我要多次改变
stone and
I'm gonna change it multiple times.
如果我还不知道有什么好名字
And if I legitimately can't
come up with any good name yet,
我以 " TODO， T-O-D-O " 开头，因为我习惯了
I start with the name TODO, T-O-D-O
because I'm in a habit of searching for
在我落实操作之前，请进行 TODO 注释。
TODO comments before I commit things.
我会找到那些未命名的函数
And I'll find those unnamed functions and
在这一点上也许能更好地理解它应该被称作什么
at that point maybe have a better
sense of what it ought to be called.
还是要努力的，还是努力，还是我的
Still a process that you have to work on,
it is still an effort, and it still my
即使这些年之后我开始用匿名的身份开始
extinctual habit even all these years
later that I start with the anonymous
但后来我意识到了这些好处然后我就回去了
function but then I realized all of these
benefits and I go back and I name them.